information about the
сведений о
patch anton
патче антон
i wanted to
мне захотелось
look i ask where is it in and how
смотрите я спрашиваю где is it in и как
do you feel about the sky wedge and
вы относитесь к небу клин а
i'll upset you i'm from russia such daisy
я вас огорчу я из россии такой дейзи
blues ask how do you feel about
сины спрашивать как вы относитесь к
pliny vinyl
винилу плиний а
and they would be very bad
у них было бы очень плохо
no war
нет войны
enmity chapter 12 and  how do you feel about
вражда chapter 12 и как вы относитесь к
it, in our opinion, the distributions [ __ ]
это их по нашему мнению раздачи пиздили
us up
нас
and why can you explain,
положить а почему вы можете объяснить
because what do you call the grandmother comes out
так как как вы называете бабушка выходит
with the flag of the USSR, he takes the flag from the grandmother
с флагом ссср он отбирает у бабушки флаг
and tramples the ground normally, and
и топчут землю нормально а
this is a video of
это видео
three videos where in a dream you know it
три видео где во сне вы знаете там
pulls but  it doesn’t mean
натягивает но это же не значит
or it doesn’t exist, you can’t look at it,
или бы нет такого не может вы досмотрите
but because of what Russia attacked Ukraine, in
а из-за чего россия напала на украину по
your opinion, the
вашему мнению
virus was brought in by troops, the client has an
вирус ввели войска у клиента есть
attack,
нападение
you will soon have connections, tell me this
вам вам скоро связи скажите это вот этот
parrot doesn’t broadcast from the side of the soul, you can’t hear it,
попугай не вещает сбоку души не слышно
put it with
отдать с
cancer  yes, I see you are standing
раком поставь да я смотрю вы там стоите
there, are you afraid of the face indicator in this they
на ли боитесь лицо показатель в этом
became slaves, as I understand it, yes
стали рабами так понимаю да
, you were in Minsk for 8 years
минске были были у вас 8 лет
, they warned that the
предупреждали предупреждали что ребята
guys were good, well, it’s
ну
not all the same, not d  it seems
хорош не все равно не доходит
that good things do
что хорошие что не доходит
n’t reach me, it just doesn’t reach me that you see
мне не доходит просто то что вы видите
get off Donetsk and Luhansk you are
отвалите от донецка и луганска вам
eight years old why we spread out
восемь лет почему мы разложили
territories and why should I destroy them
территории а зачем мне их уничтожать
such Russians destroy
таких русски уничтожает
well, yes
ну да
, until the year 2400, until the Russians came
до 2400 го года пока русские не пришли
there, everything was calm
туда все было спокойно
you were  in Donetsk more of course when I
вы были в донецке more конечно когда я
wait they don’t throw off a thread so that we are in
жду не скинут работают ниткой дабы мы в
Donetsk Yakubovich
якубович
18 18 and what is there and
18 18 и что там и
what kind of blood is there, it’s completely
что там за кровь она полностью
so good and what can I transmit now
так хорошо а что сейчас могу передавать
or let’s say that the evil Ukrainians destroyed
или допустим что злые [__] уничтожали
some outskirts of Donetsk that now
какую-то окраине донецка что сейчас
Mariupol is Russian  army
мариуполем русская армия а
and for some reason, that is, as I understand it, so
из за чего то есть я так понимаю так что
there are troops there, so some Russians,
там стоят войска так какие-то русские
so they fired at Ukrainian troops,
так они обстреляли украинские войска
though all these eight years they
правда все эти восемь лет
haven’t been there,
нет там
let’s start a chair, for example, there was such a
давайте начнем стула например там
comrade of shooters, so who
товарищ стрелков такой был так он кем
was he Ukrainian Ukrainians
был украинцем украинцам
Russian yes then  look it's
русский да то есть смотрите это
called a hybrid war when he
называется гибридная война когда
sends you under the guise of tomin 142 he told you
присылает под видом томин 142 вам сказал
that there is such a thing as
что существует такое понятие как
I used it and after that  about how I
я его вел обиход и после этого как я
deduced they began to call
вывел начали называть
and you are smart, but unlike you, I see
а вы умны но в отличии от вас вижу да
how many letters
сколько букву
you will also interrogate me, I was in a hurry for
также будете опрашивать меня я спешил
your benefit
ваша пользу
oh
ой
look, the fact is that here you are now we
смотри дело в том что вот вы сейчас мы
now have no argument about the war in
сейчас у вас нету аргументом про войну в
Ukraine you are starting to be trying not
украине вы начинаете быть пробовать не
if you want to get [ __ ], endure, that is, it turns out
доебывались терпите то есть получается
you look, you can’t even
вы смотрите вы даже без мата не можете
formulate your thought before you did it,
сформулировать свою мысль до вы делали а
but with a normal normal verb you
вот нормальным нормальным глаголом
will find out what verbs are,
узнаете что такое глаголах
well, so let’s get you
ну и так вот так давайте я вас получу
try try to formulate in
попробуй попробуйте сформулировать
normal Russian
нормальным русским языком вот нет слова
in Russian,
до выделывались в русском языке вот
try to select an analogue, you can
попробуйте подберите аналог может
get it there, twist in the brain,
получить вот вы там крутить в мозгу как
just well, but now the cartoon choice, then the bolt
раз ну но сейчас мультик выбор-то болт
blinked, let's connect and tell the
моргнул давайте подключите и скажите
memory
память
yes yes yes let's pick up some
да да да давайте нам подберите какое-то
expression so that it was from the Russian language
выражение чтоб было от русского языка
like me no
как мне нет
well then  dressed up no here take
ну то выделывались нету вот возьмите
take the words get up gave expected not
возьмите слова вставать дали ожидала не
there dress up
там выделываться
separately you do well
отдельно вы делать ну нету слова
no  rub in Russian sit not a word to show
смотрите в русском языке посиди ни слова
off here take open the
выделываться вот возьмите откройте
Dahl dictionary Ozhegov's dictionary oil method
словарь даля словарь ожегова метод масла
and so accent but in normal
и так accent а вот по нормально по
literary tell
литературному подскажите нормальным
me in normal Russian instead of the word [ __ ]
русским языком вместо слова выёбываться
and show off that you can pick up what
и выделываться что можно подобрать какое
word here I'm waiting
слово вот я жду
[music] a
[музыка]
dowry for a brush and  listen, twist in the
приданое за кисть и слушай покрутите на
language
языке
interesting in this question it’s very
интересный в этот вопрос очень
possible to show off how else you can because how can
выделываться как еще можно так как можно
you watch the phrase allowed
вы смотрите фраза допускали крути ценный
to twist valuable from get can twist this bolt
из get может подкрутить этим болтом
language can in many ways when spinning
языке может во многом при крутится
it is necessary in the brain to indoor in any way
надо в мозгу до крытый по-любому
think let’s still Russians he is
подумайте давайте все-таки русские же он
the rich are great and mighty so you saved
же богатые великий и могучий так ты спас
the walkie-talkie in it should be
у рации в нем должно быть
less than that let's finish the
менее этого давайте давайте мы закончим
site let's still we'll figure
сайте давайте все-таки мы разберемся
it out I don't know
не знаю
you explain to me here you say that you
вы мне объяснить вот вы говорите что
exhaled exhalation do I don't
выдавливались выдох делаем я не
show off
выделываться
because even you yourself said this
потому что даже вы сами сказали в этом
yoga if you can without a mat static
йогу если вы можете без мата статическом
exhalation did consider the normal Russian
выдох делали считаете нормальным русским
language of this whale layer  you don’t understand,
языком этого кита слова не понятно
well, it’s not normal and not Russian, yes,
ну не нормально и не русский да
there’s no such word, take it in the dictionary,
нет такого слова возьмите в словаре
there’s no show off,
выделываться нету
but then I checked it, let’s now
но я потом проверила давайте сейчас
we are the main ones, so what if you don’t
мы сейчас главными поэтому а вдруг вы не
check the dictionary for you, it’s more important do
проверить я тебе словарь это важнее не
n’t come in, think for you, let’s
надо войти вот подумать вам давайте
turn on our thought process and
включим наш мыслительный процесс и
let's try to think so what are
попробуем подумать так вот какие есть
the words there analogues synonyms synonyms
там слова аналоги синонимы синонимы
and antonyms homonyms hyper he
и антонимы омонимы гипер он
listens
слушает
painted me
раскрасили меня
yes I'm from Russia I'm a
да я из россии я
little bit like stealing a troll so
немножко такие украв троллю так и наши у
you don't have ours
тебя нету
how did you figure
как вы вычислили
it out y.g.  I didn’t try, I trained
это г.г. не я пробовал я тренировался
to miss eating garnet and found you like that to be lazy,
тому не хватать есть гарнет и обрела вот
they didn’t ask
такие тебя полениться они не спрашивали
you not to be lazy yuri
вас не полениться юрий
valin, I didn’t, I couldn’t say anchors through,
валин я не я не мог сказать якоря через
but I trained, I did
но я тренировался у меня получилось так
it so it’s
это
not possible to be lazy, but you can
полениться не не получается а вы можете
say like a
сказать как
meadow
поляница
but they are cunning guitar sounds,
поляница нога но они они гитарные звуки
they expel us, so I don’t know
хитрые они нас отчисляют вот я не знаю
how I kind of say it seems to me that I
как вот я вроде говорю мне кажется что я
’m talking correctly, they calculate and they
говорю правильно они вычисляют и у них
somehow differently
как-то по-другому
can be, for example, provoked there,
можно можно например там провоцировали
so if provocations, then you can,
так вот если провокации то можно
for example, a ring  and the antonym a synonym
например перстень и антоним a synonym
provoked
провоцировали
you can yes yes they provoked yes like yes
можно да да провоцировались да типа да
behaved inappropriately
вели себя неподобающим образом
if you want to steal to load then you
если ты хочешь украсть погрузить то надо
have to somehow start too because they are
как-то тоже быть начну потому что они
cunning zhike they all spend them on that I
хитрые жике они все трачу их на то
trained these ponies and methodical ones and they
натаскал эти пони и методических и это
distribute it like with
раздают как с нами разговаривает
some kind of magician is talking to us, she
какой-то маг она
said
сказала
over plus and
сверх плюс и
I, with a clear programmer, once and therefore do not
я при ясном программист раз и поэтому не
need a camera, the remark, the microphone is good,
надо камеру замечанию микрофон хорошая
quite
довольно
simple  I looked at their blogger 2 well,
простая я смотрел на у них блогера 2 ну
such nonsense they are talking about in the clearing once I looked at
такой бред несут поляне раз я смотрел на
them there, yes, like couples, but Nikita
них там есть да типа пар ну а никита
huddled, I’m all of them behind zombies a
жались я вот все они за зомбированными
lot of dough,
множко
listen to a couple of those not in the capital of
опару слушай там пару тому не в столице
tonics, God oh damn, maybe I’m them
тоников боже ой блин может быть им я
i think suyun giving them extra pay for sawing
думаю суйун дав им доплачивают за пилка
blocks
блоки
spilka
сопилка
for bloggers was called blogger.com sopilka
за блогеров назывались сопилка
, then they have such a pipe
, то дудка такой у них
or somehow at the request of the
или как-то по просьбе
community community damages spinks drank
сообщества сообщества дамажит спинкс пил
cola about a year split splinter type on a
колу про год спилка спилковые типа на
barefoot file it’s a spirit they have such a there
боса пилка это духа у них такая там дети
his children  kisses the genocide from the type and
его целует геноциде от типа а
I, I still have a flag for myself a minute ago, I
я я еще флаг себе минуту назад я
specifically found the treasure, of course, damn
специально нашел клад искал конечно блин
you, my friend sewed me because
тебя меня знакомая пошила потому что у
we don’t sell
нас не продаются
Ukrainian ones,
украинских
they
у
have a bunch of these donors, I think that the
них куча этих донорах я думаю что им
West is now throwing loot
сейчас запад кидает бабло
to them in order to competently
для того чтобы грамотно
then over it  not in Ukraine, these Ukrainians are
тогда над это не украине украинцы эти
throwing at him like this, they are sitting in the West, here are these
ему кидают так это сидят запада вот эти
constructions of Germany, the British, the ocean of
конструкции германии британцы океан
classes
классов
there Donat,
там донат
here we have that our blogger, how much the
вот у нас что нашим блогером я сколько
law is there 50 rubles, and they have 300
закон там 50 рублей а у них там 300
gr there  iven and
гривен и
not someone on ti3 money will not be well, yes,
не кто-то на ти3 деньги не будет ну да
because 300 hryvnia 300 hryvnia then 27
потому что 300 гривен 300 гривен то 27
hundred rubles and received 100 rubles there in the form
сот рублей и получил 100 рублей там виде
of him in dollars, even dana does
на him в долларах даже дана делает
it means I watched them there is this site
значит я смотрел них есть этот сайт
patreon and one dollar does not come there  5
patreon и не приходит там один доллар 5
dollars 10 dollars pissing dollars and
долларов 10 долларов пися доллары и
donating, that is, it turns out that these are
донатят то есть получается они вот эти
visible from her diaspora there from different countries of
видно из нее диаспора там с разных стран
Europe samira [ __ ] should be on the tag, I
европы самире киска надо надо на тег я
think that they are not just a diaspora there and
думаю что им там не просто диаспора и
those who still think somewhere there are the CIA and the mi-  6
думающим все-таки где-то там цру и ми-6
gives out some kind of budgets and they seem to be
выдаёт какие то бюджеты и они вроде как
distributing this diaspora to these bloggers under the guise of this diaspora
под видом вот эта диаспоры раздают этими
and the bloggers
блогерам а блогеры
sit all day and
целый день сидят и вот так русским
brainwash the Russians like this, it’s unrealistic
промывают мозги то это что же нереально
here we are working with you where
вот мы с вами работаем где такого целый
they sit all day and do roulette for
день они сидят и в рулетке делаю под
10  -20-30 the wick doesn't even work
10-20-30 фитилька даже не работает
really
правда
action
экшн
and what do they have to do with them however and okay
и при чем они они однако и ну ладно
well everything is happy
хорошо все счастлив
show
покажите